Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Let's go!
This world is colorful and bright
Truth and lies confuse our eyes
Look carefully with your heart
The truth is just a thought away
Hey you, good or bad, true or false
You can't escape this trial of the heart
Take all your courage with you
Maybe you can save this world
Enraged Lord Eye merges with Phoenix Chicken
Becomes a giant monster
Launches a devastating attack on Locky and the others
Can they defeat this crazed behemoth?
Grand Finale
I finally got to save you once, too
I won't fail to repay your kindness
Is this... what feelings are?
Big Ugly Bird
You think just 'cause you're big, you can bully people
I'll show you what I've got!
Here I come!
After all that fighting, I forgot...
His weakness is that gem!
The gem!
Hurry up!
Big stinky bird
Damn it!
Still no way?
I have an idea.
For Love and Ideals? Give me a break!
You actually smashed my most treasured magnifying glass!
So I'm going to help you!
You know, The Illumin-Eye summoned by the flames at the corporation
Once it's fully opened,
the entire world will be flooded by Storm and seawater.
The only way to stop The Illumin-Eye from opening is
to put out these eight flames!
Now's the time!
Come on!
Okay!
Let's join forces and take him down.
Are you ready?
Ready!
Let's show him what we've got!
I'm ashamed I couldn't help when it mattered most.
Detective Chen
Don't say that.
Everyone here is a hero.
Nobody was afraid to make sacrifices.
Is he
sacrificing himself?
Take that!!
Locky!
Yeah.
It's all over.
What a pity.
The Illumin-Eye escaped.
The Illumin-Eye will definitely make a comeback!
But little Locky, he—
Uncle, we all came to see you.
Uncle, you're so useless.
You actually got hurt this badly.
Oh right, today I have my favorite math class.
I'll come see you again after school.
Bye-bye.
Who'd have thought
Ever since Locky defeated The Illumin-Eye with math problems,
he'd actually be so into school.
Locky's finally willing to go to school.
Hurry, Jingjing, we're going to be late.
Locky!
Wait for me!
I really don't want to be alone and lonely.
But life is bound to have some unhappiness.
Saying goodbye to today always leaves you feeling a little lost
Looking to tomorrow, waving at me from the horizon
Bright eyes are sparkling
A smile that faces the sunlight
Bravely speak out that tiny feeling treasured deep in your heart
The morning breeze blows softly across my face
Taking childhood wishes away
It will quietly plant them at the crossroads of growing up